

CONTACT

rajisebutu@gmail.com

(832) 258 1009

www.remilekunajisebutu.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/r emilekun-ajisebutu-25a026a5/

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: MANAGEMENT AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

2013

Wisconsin International University College - Accra, Ghana

MASTER OF SCIENCE : MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS

2018

Texas Southern University- Jesse H. Jones School of Business - Houston, TX

TECHNICAL SKILLS

 HTML

CSS3 JavaScript

Microsoft Office Suite

Jira

Azure DeVops

SharePoint

SQL

Java

Python

Selenium

Tableau

Plotly

R-Analysis

Figma

Perfecto

REMILEKUN AJISEBUTU

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A forward-thinking, capable and committed with overall 5 years experience in Information Technology, Software Quality and Data Analysis gained in various organizations globally. Extensively analyzed, designed, developed, tested and implemented applications in various industries including Finance, Oil and Gas, Telecommunications, Public Sector and Consulting.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

Quality Engineering
Consulting
Team Leadership
Web Design
Project Management
Frontend Development

Database Administration
Data Analysis
Machine Learning
Agile Framework
Conservational Al
Automation Testing

EXPERIENCESTEST LEAD

Accenture Technology - Tanium and Active Defense Server | Oct 2021 - Present

- Leading the Infrastructure Testing team of 3 testers to help deploy Tanium cloud solutions
- Working across team and vendor to troubleshoot and resolve complex issues
- Providing expertise in the planning, constructing and execution of over 100 test scripts
- Develop testing plans and ensuring all testing results are easily accessible and understandable through Azure DeVops
- Gathering requirement from clients to achieve the suitable test approach that is targeted at their testing deficit.

TESTER

Accenture Technology - Keybank | Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

- Conducted QA testing to ensure usability of the voice channel and web chat bot with 100% client satisfaction
- Performed sanity testing when a new deployment occurs in an environment
- Performed UI testing on Web and Mobile devices for various features
- Tracked and updated testing activities in the JIRA collaborative tool so that there's visibility between team members
- Supported team lead by understanding and complying to the projects objectives, performance standards and policies.

INFRASTRUCTURE TECHNICAL SPECIALIST

Accenture Technology - Accenture CIO | Jun 2019- Feb 2021

- Deployed the TDS guest check-in tool for the RTO(Return to Office) initiative to over 300
 Accenture sites Globally
- Assisted over 300 Local Technical Specialists(LTS) globally in the procurement and configuration of their Hardware to run the TDS guest check-in tool
- Developed the configuration guide, performed testing on the hardware before rolling out to the sites
- Developed a SharePoint site to manage major data points for over Accenture 800 sites and tracked deployment proggress.



REMILEKUN AJISEBUTU

EXPERIENCES

GRADUATE TEACHING ASSISTANT

Texas Southern University | Sep 2017 - Dec 2018

- Utilized 20+ hours per week to develop and design individual methodologies for diverse student abilities to cut studying and augment efficiency in lecture and laboratory courses
- Worked individual with all students who did not score higher than 65% on the first two exam and successfully. Boosted their averages by at least 10%
- Provided technical support to students in the computer labs
- Provided feedback to students learning achievements and areas that need improvement.

SCANNING TECHNICIAN

Katalyst Data Management | Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

- Scanned over 1m seismic support documentation, including observer logs, survey notes and seismic sections
- Organized incoming data based on assigned priority level
- Initiated communication with Team Lead to solve problems related to documents.

DATA/IT ANALYST

Olad Petroleum Ltd | Mar 2015 - Dec 2016

- · Responsible for maintaining database and reporting any issues immediately to management
- Using statistical tools to identify, analyze, and interpret patterns and trends in complex data sets that could be helpful for the diagnosis and prediction
- Removing corrupted data and fixing coding errors and related problems
- Filter Data by reviewing reports and performance indicators to identify and correct code problems.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner AWS | 2020
- Professional Scrum Master (PSM1) Scrum.org | 2021

TRAININGS AND BOOTCAMPS

- The University of Texas at Austin Red McCombs School of Business Data Analysis Bootcamp | 2021
- Platform by PerSholas Bootcamp Quality Engineering | 2018
- Lagos Andela Information and Communication Technology (ICT) Program | 2017
- The Future Project Entrepreneurship Unveiled Intensive Training | 2015

MEMBERSHIPS

- Professional Member- Association of Computing Machinery
- Professional Member National Society for Black Engineers

ACCOMPLISHMENT & INTERESTS

- Founder Nutreatie Foods
- Recipient of JHJ Graduate Scholarship and Assistantship TSU
- Entrepreneur of the year- Lagos Andela ICT Program

VOLUNTEERING

- Career Advisor Back on my Feet | 2020
- Instructor Hour of Code | 2021
- Instructor Bold Idea | 2021
- Volunteer Black Girls Code | 2022